dreamhomebasedwork.com 2019-12-20

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

 _Last updated: February 13, 2019  _

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.dreamhomebasedwork.com. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our [homepage](https://www.dreamhomebasedwork.com/) and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

[toc]

##  **Introduction**

Welcome to [www.dreamhomebasedwork.com](https://www.dreamhomebasedwork.com/) (“Website,” “Site,” or “Service”) owned and operated by Dream Home Based Work a business operating in accordance with the State laws of Florida and the federal laws of the United States of America (hereinafter “Company,” “We,” “Us,” or “Our”). Any reference in this Privacy Policy to the “User,” “You” or “Your,” refers to you, the User or Website Visitor and any reference to the Company, refer to us, the Company. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, the Company is the data controller.

We respect your privacy and are committed to providing full transparency regarding how we collect and use your personal information and with whom we share this personal information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to familiarize yourself with our practices regarding the collection and use of your personal data. We urge you not to use the Website and provide us with any personal information if you do not expressly agree with our collection and use of your personal data as described hereunder. By using our Website, you hereby give us your express consent to the collection and use of your Personal Information as stated herein.

##  **Information we collect**

The Information you provide us voluntarily

When you subscribe to receive marketing material from our website, you voluntarily provide us with your email address. Currently, this is the only information you voluntarily provide through our website. We may request you to provide additional information in the future. In the event we request any additional information, we will update this Privacy Policy accordingly. 

Linkable information we collect through your use of our service:

There is certain information that we are able to collect about you that can be used to identify you. This information is automatically collected using technologies such as cookies and web beacons. It enables us to collect information about you such as your IP address, your browser type or version, the pages you visit on our Website as well as date and time of your visit.

##  **How we use the information we collect**

We use your personally identifiable information to: 

  * Deliver our services to you; 
  * Contact you if required; 
  * Inform you about the important service and policy updates.

We use your linkable information to improve our understanding of how you use our Service and to improve your user experience.

Please note that with the exception of acquisition or merger, we will not sell your personally identifiable information to any third-party for any commercial gain whatsoever. 

## **Marketing Communications**

We use the Personal information you provide us with to inform you about changes or updates to the Website or to send promotional material to you. You can select to stop receiving communication from us, at any time, by simply clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our email or by simply contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#472f222b2b2807233522262a2f282a2225263422233028352c6924282a). 

##  **Sharing your information**

We may share your personal information with third-party service providers that we may engage to help us in facilitating our Website. 

We may also share your personal information with our service providers who assist us with intelligent analysis of how our Users interact with our Website. We will always take steps to ensure that these Service Providers are bound by our confidentiality agreements to ensure that they do not disclose any personal information about our Users to any other person or entity apart from us.

We also make use of a third-party tool like ConvertKit to capture your email when you subscribe through our Website. ConvertKit is a US Limited Liability Company and complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Data transferred from the European Union and European Economic Area and Switzerland to the United States. 

## **Compliance with the law**

Please note that we may disclose your personal information to the extent required by law in order to be in compliance with our legal obligations and/or official investigations if such requests are initiated by any government authority or law enforcement officials upon reasonable requests.

##  **Cookies**

We make use of cookies on our Website. 

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small files with data that we use to identify you as a unique User. We do not associate any of your Personal Information with these unique identifier files. We send cookies to your browser from our website, and these cookies are stored on your computer’s hard drive. You can tell your browser to decline all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. In the event that you decide to decline cookies from our Website, you may not be able to use some parts of our Service. We use cookies to improve your user experience on our Website. 

**How long do cookies remain on my device?**

We use session cookies as well as persistent cookies on our Website. Session cookies are immediately deleted from your hard drive after the end of your browser session. However, persistent cookies remain on your hard drive for a minimum period of time unless you clear them manually from your device. 

**Don’t want to accept cookies?**

You can set your default browser setting to reject cookies from third-party websites. To learn more about cookies, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

## **Security of your data**

We strive to keep all your Personal Information secure. We use all commercially viable means and industry best practices to protect your Personal Information, but our software and service are built upon various other software and hardware components that may have security vulnerabilities, which is why we are unable to offer any guarantees of its security. 

## **Transfer of data**

We will transfer and process your personally identifiable information on computers and servers that are located in the United States of America and other parts of the world where the data protection laws may differ from those of the country where you currently reside. If you are currently residing in one of the member states in European Economic Area (EEA), you understand and consent to your personally identifiable information being transferred outside of the EEA and processed in the United States of America. 

## **Third-party website links**

Our Website may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or operated by us. Should you decide to click on any such third party links, You will be directed to such third party website. These third-party sites have their own Terms and Privacy Policy, and we encourage you to review their Terms and Privacy Policy prior to using their site or any services offered by them.

We cannot be held responsible for any content made available by these third-party sites or their practices. You access and use these sites solely at your own risk.

##  **Protection of Children’s Privacy**

Our website and services are not addressed for anyone under the age of thirteen (13) years (“Children”). If you are the parent or legal guardian of a Child who you believe has provided us with his/her personally identifiable information, please contact us immediately, and we will take steps to remove such personally identifiable information from our database and servers immediately.

##  **Modification**

We may modify and update this Privacy Policy at any time at our sole discretion. In the event we modify this Privacy Policy, We will inform you by changing the last updated date on the top. You are advised to review this Policy periodically. Please take note that any changes will be effective when posted on this web page.

##  **Your Rights**

You have the right to request access to your personally identifiable information that we hold and to update or edit this information to ensure it is current and accurate. Please note that in order to ensure the safety of your data, we may need to verify your identity before we grant you access to your personal information. We will only retain your personal data as long as necessary to deliver our service to you or to assist us in resolving any disputes that are either anticipated or ongoing. 

To exercise your right to access your personal information, you may contact us at the contact details provided below with the words “personal information” in the subject line. 

##  **California Privacy Rights Notice**

IF YOU ARE A CALIFORNIA RESIDENT AND YOU HAVE PROVIDED ANY PERSONAL DATA TO US, YOU MAY REQUEST INFORMATION ABOUT WHETHER WE HAVE DISCLOSED YOUR  PERSONAL INFORMATION TO ANY THIRD-PARTIES FOR SUCH THIRD-PARTY’S DIRECT MARKETING PURPOSES. WHERE WE HAVE MADE SUCH DISCLOSURE TO THIRD-PARTIES FOR SUCH THIRD-PARTY’S DIRECT MARKETING PURPOSES, AS A  CALIFORNIA RESIDENT, YOU CAN REQUEST US TO PROVIDE YOU A LIST OF ALL THIRD PARTIES TO WHOM PERSONAL DATA WAS DISCLOSED IN THE PRECEDING YEAR ALONG WITH THE LIST OF CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA DISCLOSED. IF YOU WISH TO LEARN MORE ABOUT OUR COMPLIANCE, PLEASE CONTACT US AT [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#274f424b4b4867435542464a4f484a4245465442435048554c0944484a). 

## **Contact Us**

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#c6aea3aaaaa986a2b4a3a7abaea9aba3a4a7b5a3a2b1a9b4ade8a5a9ab).
